<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mathieu @ GRAAL</title>
    <link>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mathieu @ GRAAL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mathieualain.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Master</title>
      <link>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/msc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 13:23:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/msc/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m delighted to stay in the realm of the GRAAL research group under the guidance of François Laviolette for my MSc in Computer Science. A new set of challenges and opportunities is forthcoming!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRAAL</title>
      <link>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/graal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 13:23:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/graal/</guid>
      <description>I’m glad to be part of the GRAAL research group for the summer. The group is led by François Laviolette and Mario Marchand and their interests cover machine learning and its practical applications. I&amp;rsquo;m new to machine learning, but it should be fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GIREF</title>
      <link>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/giref/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 13:23:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/giref/</guid>
      <description>This summer I will join the GIREF research group under the supervision of José Urquiza. Their main focus is numerical methods commonly used in engineering such as the finite element method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RAMiCS 2017</title>
      <link>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/ramics2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:23:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/ramics2017/</guid>
      <description>I’m happy to announce that the paper with Jules Desharnais titled Relation as Images has been accepted at RAMiCS 2017. Therefore, I’ll be in Lyon (France) in early May to present our recent work. This paper primarily defines two basic morphological operations (dilation and erosion) on binary images using a formalism from relation algebra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LSFM</title>
      <link>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/lfsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 13:23:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mathieualain.github.io/post/lfsm/</guid>
      <description>I’m thrilled to join the LSFM research group for the summer under the supervision of Jules Desharnais. Their interests lie in languages, semantics, formal and algebraic methods. I couldn’t ask for a better first research experience!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>